<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Department Introduction | ACSSZ</title><link>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/</link><atom:link href="https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Department Introduction</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://acssz.github.io/media/icon_hu4762e5b73ec87b3d5faf551939ac0d6d_330821_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Department Introduction</title><link>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/</link></image><item><title>Department of Sport and Recreation</title><link>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/wenti/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/wenti/</guid><description>&lt;p>As the sports department of the Students&amp;rsquo; Federation, our goal is to call on everyone to join us: Move! We spare no effort to organize rich and interesting sports competitions for you, but also provide a broad platform for you to find like-minded partners to play sports together. If you are a sports person, you want to find more friends to learn from each other and improve each other; Or if you are interested in organizing sports activities and want to organize better games for your friends, you are welcome to join us!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Department of Technology</title><link>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/jishu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/jishu/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Technology Department has been recruiting students&amp;rsquo; Association app, forum, website, small program and other developers for a long time, welcome students who are enthusiastic about technology to join!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Department</title><link>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/qiye/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/qiye/</guid><description>&lt;p>The enterprise department is mainly responsible for visiting enterprises, maintaining good relations with enterprises and recruiting enterprises. At the same time, we will seek sponsorship from different enterprises according to different activities. Joining the enterprise requires a high level of ability in all aspects, but you will also gain more!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The company wants you to be enthusiastic, sincere, eloquent, and good at English (German will be a plus). If you think you can, you are welcome to give it a try!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Public Relations Department</title><link>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/gongguan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/gongguan/</guid><description>&lt;p>Maintain internal and external public relations to better meet the work, study and life needs of Zurich students：&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Contacted outstanding talents in work, travel and hobbies, shared experiences online and offline for students; Compiling new student handbook; Organize Zurich Parade Group, self-defense instruction, volunteers, Dragon Boat Festival reunion and other activities.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Communication and liaison with ETH start-ups, co-organizing innovation and entrepreneurship competitions, experience sharing and other activities; Chinese students in Switzerland entrepreneurship research, write entrepreneurship report; Communicate and cooperate with the alumni Association and other student associations at home and abroad.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Communicate with China Switzerland Connection, China Switzerland Connection, Association of Science and Technology, Ruilong Ski Association, Jingwu Hall, art troupe, etc., and organize Sino-Switzerland cultural exchange, language corner, cultural festival, martial arts class, artistic performance and other activities. 4. Responsible for the connection with the embassy and consulates and assist the work of the embassy and consulates.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>The classmates in Zurich seem to know everyone&amp;rsquo;s name (it is very easy to meet students from all over the world, flirt with girls, flirt with handsome boys, and foreign girls and handsome boys); You also know all the great people in Zurich. (As the saying goes, there must be a teacher in the company of three. There are so many teachers. The cultivation of interpersonal skills. Working in public relations and dealing with so many people, emotional intelligence comes naturally. Organizational leadership. To successfully organize an activity, it is a great exercise of Leadership, in the future, all kinds of leaderless group discussions, naturally won&amp;rsquo;t be afraid.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Want to exercise students work ability; Want to broaden your relationships; Want to develop leadership skills; Most importantly, you want to work with us, to serve the students, to make the ideas in your head come true.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Public Relations Department</title><link>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/wailian/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/wailian/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Public Relations Department is mainly responsible for organizing information conferences and job fairs held in Zurich by domestic governments, universities and enterprises.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Whether you want to get first-hand information about employment in China, want to build a network in China, want to practice the ability of organization, communication and coordination, or want to make friends in Sucun, the Public Relations Department welcomes you to join!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Secreariat</title><link>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/mishu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://acssz.github.io/en/about/group/mishu/</guid><description>&lt;p>The success of Student Federation activities cannot be achieved without the behind-the-scenes assistance of our secretary Department. We&amp;rsquo;ve never been known, but we&amp;rsquo;re decathlon, we&amp;rsquo;re everywhere, we know all the action. We set up an organized file system and email system, we help organize meetings, and we&amp;rsquo;re head of finance, head of human resources&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In short, if you want to keep a low-key luxury and connotation of the temperament, but also want to do something, the secretariat welcomes you.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>